mmorpg.com 2011-06-01

# Online MMO and MMORPG Gamelist, News, Reviews and Community at MMORPG.com

## Terms of Use

MMORPG.COM (a Web site operated wholly by Cyber Creations Inc.) provides this site as a resource for the MMORPG community. Forum posts can be deleted and users may be banned from this site, without prior warning or explanation, at the sole discretion of Cyber Creations Inc.

You must be _at least 13 years_ of age to use this Web site. Persons under the age of 13 **MUST** obtain a parent's or guardian's permission prior to using this Web site.

## Forums / Chat / Messaging Rules

### Our Goal

We have not set out to limit people's freedom of speech or discussion. These rules simply strive to keep the boards on topic, productive and inclusive for all members. Accidental violation of minor rules will not result in strict penalties. We want our users to enjoy our boards and feel that these rules will ensure that everyone can equally.

### Minor Infractions

Committing Minor Infractions at MMORPG.com will result in a first warning, followed by temporary bans. If the issue becomes chronic, a permanent ban will be considered.

* For purposes of our rules, we will work under a 3 strikes policy. A first offense results in a warning. A second offence results in a 1 to 14 day ban and a third offence results in a lengthy and possibly permanent ban. Warnings and bans remain active for these purposes for 6 months. Note that severe offenses may receive stronger action, even on first or second offenses.

  * Religion and Politics 
    * MMORPG.com is a site to discuss massively multiplayer online roleplay gaming. While users are encouraged and permitted to use our Off-Topic forum to discuss real life and non-MMORPG gaming, threads concerning sensitive subjects such as religion, politics, or ethics may be locked or deleted if determined out of hand by the MMORPG.com moderator staff.
  * Language Policy 
    * MMORPG.com wishes to create the friendliest atmosphere possible in our forums and on our site. As such, excessive use of strong language will not be tolerated. Ex: The odd "bad word" is fine. A profanity laced rant, on the other hand, is not. Discretion will rest with the moderators.
  * Topic Hijacking 
    * Posting comments within a thread which severely disrupts the original conversation is prohibited at MMORPG.com.  
_Example: Asking whether a game has PvP in a thread about crafting materials found in a new expansion is Topic Hijacking._
  * Flaming and Personal Attacks 
    * MMORPG.com does not tolerate personal attacks on other posters. Please keep your arguments and posts on topic, and argue the ideas and topics of the thread instead of insulting other users.  
_Example: Telling someone that you disagree with their argument is tolerated, while calling someone inappropriate names is not._
  * Game Attacks 
    * Unsubstantiated comments about specific or general games will be penalized in nearly the same way attacks against people will. The exception is that you can say mean things about games provided you back it up with reasons.  
_Example: "Game X sucks." is not a legitimate comment. "Game X sucks, because..." is acceptable._
  * Spamming "Post Report" Tool 
    * We encourage users to report posts that they feel violate these rules, but if you spam or abuse the report tool, penalties will apply.  
_Example: Reporting a post we do not take action is not against the rules. Reporting the same post dozens of times, is._
  * Using the Post Report Tool as a Method of Contacting the Moderators 
    * The post report tool is not intended to be used as a way for users to communicate with Moderators. If you have an issue with a warning or ban, please email [community@mmorpg.com](mailto:community@mmorpg.com).
  * Referral Links 
    * MMORPG.com does not support its members posting links for which they are entitled to reward. This constitutes advertising on the forums. If you wish to purchase advertising with us, please contact [admin@mmorpg.com](mailto:admin@mmorpg.com).
  * Trolling 
    * Posting excessive negative comments or baiting others to respond in a negative manner is considered trolling on the MMORPG.com forums.  
_For example: If there is one game that you did not enjoy, voicing your opinion is encouraged. Posting this opinion in every thread concerning that game to the point that it disrupts all other conversation is not tolerated._
  * Copyright and Press Material 
    * Reposting material in its entirety from other sources is against our rules. Quotations from things such as news articles are fine, provided it is cited and (if possible) linked to. We ask others to respect our content and ask our readers do the same for other people's content.
  * NDAs 
    * MMORPG.com does not permit users to post information on games still under an NDA. For more information about your specific game's NDA, please visit their official website.
  * Off-Topic Posting 
    * Posting in boards that clearly have nothing to do with your topic is not tolerated. Typically, posts of this nature will be moved to the appropriate board.  
_Example: A post in the EverQuest II boards about how much you love World of WarCraft is off topic._
  * Virtual Trading 
    * MMORPG.com does not allow the purchase, sale, or trade of in-game assets, accounts, or powerleveling services.
  * Individual Forum Rules 
    * Some MMORPG.com forums have individual rule sets â€“ please check the forum description and any stickied topics for more detailed information.

### Medium Infractions

At the discretion of the moderator and/or the Community Manager, the following infractions will be classed as either minor or major infractions and appropriate penalties will be applied.

  * Inappropriate Signatures 
    * Signatures may not contain material that breaches MMORPG.com Rules of Conduct.
  * Spamming 
    * Posting the same or similar messages over and over again for the sole purpose of disrupting a board's activity is against the rules.
  * Advertisements 
    * MMORPG.com does not allow users to advertise products or companies in our forums. If you want to advertise, contact [admin@mmorpg.com](mailto:admin@mmorpg.com).
  * Resurrecting Locked or Deleted Threads 
    * If a thread has previously been deleted or locked by a moderator, it is against our rules to start another thread on the same topic. This rule applies if a participant in a locked or deleted thread re-starts the thread, a warning and 1 day ban will be issued. If this happens twice, the member will be permanently banned, no exceptions.
  * Unofficial Servers 
    * Discussing or advertising unofficial servers or emulators for MMOs is not permitted on the MMORPG.com forums. These servers are against the Terms of Service of the original game, and violate the intellectual propriety rights of the game's publisher and developer.
  * 3rd Party Programs 
    * MMORPG.com does not allow forum discussion concerning programs that go against a game's EULA. This includes, but is not limited to, third party programs to automate gameplay or gain an unfair advantage over other players. Please check with your specific game's EULA for more details on what is or isn't allowed.

### Major Infractions

Committing Major Infractions at MMORPG.com will result in an immediate and permanent ban from the site with no pervious warnings or infractions. The is no room for leniency or discussion

  * Hateful Content 
    * Hateful content includes, but is not limited to, discriminating comments about: race, ethnicity (what country someone is from), religion, age, gender, sexuality, socioeconomic status and political beliefs. MMORPG.com holds complete and total discretion to decide what is hateful.
  * Pornographic Images 
    * MMORPG.com has subscribers of all ages and beliefs. Posting any pornographic images, content or links, no matter what the medium, will not be tolerated. At the discretion of the moderators and community manager, this rule will also be extended to include images of an erotic nature.
  * Illegal Activities 
    * Either committing or the discussion of committing illegal activities at MMORPG.com will not be tolerated. Illegal activities include, but are not limited to: illegal drugs, fraud, violence, hacking, software piracy and sexual harassment. As appropriate, illegal activities will be reported to the relevant law enforcement agency.
  * Multiple Accounts 
    * If the staff of MMORPG.com discovers that a user is creating and/or using multiple accounts, that user, and all accounts, both past and present, will be banned from MMORPG.com.
  * Posting Other's Personal Information Without Consent 
    * It is against our rules to post the personal information of other people without their consent. This includes, but is not limited to, email correspondence, contact information, photographs, financial information and social security numbers. It is to the moderator's discretion to decide whether or not the line has been crossed.

## Game List

### Ratings and Hype-meter

In regards to game ratings and hype-meter voting, we reserve the right to remove unfairly obtained votes and, as needed, suspend voting on games deemed to have been given unfair votes. The amount of time voting will be suspended is dependent upon how long MMORPG.com believes it will take before fair voting will again occur.

In the case of ratings and hype-meter votes, "unfair votes" are determined by MMORPG.com staff and specifically include (but are not limited to):

  * Those solicited by game companies asking for a particular rating ("go rate our game a 10").
  * Those solicited by game companies offering any kind of compensation or contest.
  * Those registered by single users under multiple accounts.

* * *

MMORPG.COM is committed to protecting your privacy. This statement of privacy defines and governs how we gather and use data at this Web site.

## Collection of Your Personal Information

We gather personal information from all registering members. This includes name, physical address, e-mail address, age and gender. We also store your personal preferences related to this Web site in your account data.

We also collect data relating to all network connections, primarily your IP address. We use this information to track fraudulent user activity (including but not limited to: the use of multiple accounts, account sharing, illegal forum activity.) Your browser type and version are also detected to better enhance your user experience.

We keep track of what polls you have voted in to prevent duplicate voting. This data is stored with your user account data.

Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information through our messaging system, public forms, or chat rooms - this information could be collected and used by other parties.

MMORPG.COM encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites that you choose to link to from MMORPG.COM so that you know how those web sites collect and use your personal information.

## How We Use Your Personal Information

Your physical location, gender, date of membership and last login date is used in your MMORPG.COM "User Profile" to create a better sense of community at our site. In addition we give you the option of displaying your e-mail address and age. If you wish to hide this data, you can do so in the "Your Account Settings" page.

During the account creation process the user has the ability to "opt-in" to two separate mailing lists:

  * MMORPG.COM Newsletter 
    * Our newsletter is only sent from us, and no more than once per week. This service is used to notify our members about the status of the site and current events. This newsletter might contain advertisements or endorsements as a smaller part of the message, but never for this sole purpose.
  * MMORPG.COM Daily Digest 
    * Our daily digest is only sent from us once per day 5 days a week monday through friday. This service is used to notify our members about the status of the site and current events. The daily digest might contain advertisements or endorsements as a smaller part of the message, but never for this sole purpose.
  * Promotional Mailing 
    * This list will be used to notify our members of special promotions taking place related to MMORPG games. It will only be sent from us. These offers can be for beta test offers or other promotions from us or other game companies. This mailing will never be sent more than four times per month.

**NOTE:** MMORPG.COM _never_ sells or shares any of your personal information with other parties. All information is strictly for internal use and all e-mails are only sent from our facilities.

You can change your subscription to either of these mailings by updating your account profile by selecting "Your Account Settings" and then modifying the options in "Alert Settings".

MMORPG.COM may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our company or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of our company, including the MMORPG.COM Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of MMORPG.COM, its web sites, or the public.

## Securing Your Personal Information

MMORPG.COM takes all necessary measures to protect your personal information by deploying safe network models for storing and retrieving data. All credit card data is sent over secure SSL connections using 128-bit encryption.

## Use of Cookies

A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

MMORPG.COM uses cookies to store your preferences at our site and to track the "session state" of your visit. If you choose to use our "auto-login" feature, we store your username and password using a simple encryption technique in a cookie on your computer.

We never use cookies to gather or share your personal information.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to access the MMORPG.COM site - as our site requires them to function properly and prevent site abuse.

* * *

This web site is the exclusive property of Cyber Creations Inc. and may not be copied or reproduced without written permission. All graphics are the property of, or licensed by, Cyber Creations Inc., for use within this Web site.

All game logos, or game-specific designs are used by permission by the individual publishing company. These images are copyrighted by their respective owners. These images may not be copied or reproduced without permission from their respective owners.

**Copyright © Cyber Creations Inc. 2002-2011**
